

Ahmed Yacine Bouchouareb

Upcoming Graduate in Artificial Intelligence and Data Science from ESTIN Bejaia.

Fifth-year student specializing in Artificial Intelligence and Data Science at ESTIN Bejaia. I have extensive experience in software development with a focus on front-end, as well as full-stack skills. Versatile, I have explored UI/UX design, game development, cybersecurity, and completed freelance projects. Recently, I completed a final-year internship as a research intern in Machine learning at UDES in Canada. My goal is to apply and further develop my skills in Ai and software development.

bayacine9919@gmail.com

PEl kala, Algérie

in linkedin.com/in/ahmedyacinebouchouareb

0793706484

bayacineportfolio.netlify.app/

github.com/chechna9

EDUCATION

Advanced Classes

ECOLE SUPÉRIEURE EN SCIENCES ET TECHNOLOGIES DE L'INFORMATIQUE ET DU NUMÉRIQUE (ESTIN)

11/2021 - Present Bejaia, Amizour

Relevant Coursework

Databases

Software Engineering

Artificial Intelligence

ice

Deep Learning

Advanced Statistics

Data Analysis

Preparatory ClassesECOLE NATIONALE SUPERIEURE

D'INFORMATIQUE (ESI)

11/2019 - 11/2021 Relevant Coursework Agiers, Oued Semar

Algorithms and Data

 Algorithms and Data Structures Assembly

 Object-Oriented Programming Computer Architecture

Calculus

Algebra

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Research Intern in Artificial Intelligence Université de Sherbrooke

02/2024 - 07/2024 Sherbrooke, Canada Tasks

- Conducted a literature review on the robustness of machine learning against adversarial attacks.
- Developed a pipeline to automate the generation and classification of adversarial attacks in the context of anomaly detection.

Software Engineering InternshipElexTranslate

06/2023 - 07/2023

remote

Task

 Development of a translation platform using React.js, Flask, and AWS

Développement web et mobileFreelance

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Kurio App (08/2023 - 11/2023)

- A mobile application using generative AI to create educational content for children
- Won third place at the international hackathon "Africa to Silicon Valley."

Valorant Win Prediction (04/2023 - 05/2023) 🗷

- From data collection to an AI-based web application for predicting victories in games.
- The rest is available on my portfolio and GitHub account.

CERTIFICATES

Machine Learning

12 weeks course by AndrewNG

Deep Learning

4 weeks course by AndrewNG

Responsive Web Design

300 hours course from freecodeCamp

LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

French

C2 (TCF 2023)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

GDG Algiers member

ByteCraft member

Flutter Trainer

Git/Github Trainer